goldsilverreports.com 2019-04-01

# PRIVACY POLICY ⋆ Gold Silver Reports

This website is administered by GoldSilverreports.com. We want you to feel secure when visiting our site and are committed to maintaining your privacy when doing so. The following provides an overview of how we protect your privacy during your visit to our site.

## Information we collect

Information on goldsilverreports.com is gathered when you provide information across various pages on goldsilverreports.com.

We collect information directly from you in a number of ways, some of which are described in this Privacy Statement. One way is through the use of cookies. Cookies are small files of information which save and retrieve information about your visit to goldsilverreports.com for example, how you entered our site, how you navigated through the site, and what information was of interest to you.

## Is your Private Data Safe?

As a commited organization, the data we collect will not be leaked outside our organization in any ways. In the event of a merger, consolidation, collaboration or reorganization involving www.goldsilverreports.com, your personal information will, in most instances, be transferred to the control of the third party that is part of that transaction. So, before you submit any information, we will notify you as to why we are asking for specific information and it is completely up to you whether or not you want to provide it.

## Personal Data

We are committed to protecting your personal information and do so with certain physical and technological procedures. However, we cannot ensure the security of the information as you transmit it to us, and so we urge you to take every precaution to protect your personal data when you are on the Internet. This includes using a secure browser like Mozilla Firefox, Google Chrome, Sea Monkey, Netscape or Opera where applicable. We do not recommend Internet Explorer.

## Who we are

Our website address is: https://www.goldsilverreports.com.

## What personal data we collect and why we collect it

### Comments

When visitors leave comments on the site we collect the data shown in the comments form, and also the visitor’s IP address and browser user agent string to help spam detection.

An anonymized string created from your email address (also called a hash) may be provided to the Gravatar service to see if you are using it. The Gravatar service privacy policy is available here: https://automattic.com/privacy/. After approval of your comment, your profile picture is visible to the public in the context of your comment.

### Media

If you upload images to the website, you should avoid uploading images with embedded location data (EXIF GPS) included. Visitors to the website can download and extract any location data from images on the website.

### Contact forms

### Cookies

If you leave a comment on our site you may opt-in to saving your name, email address and website in cookies. These are for your convenience so that you do not have to fill in your details again when you leave another comment. These cookies will last for one year.

If you have an account and you log in to this site, we will set a temporary cookie to determine if your browser accepts cookies. This cookie contains no personal data and is discarded when you close your browser.

When you log in, we will also set up several cookies to save your login information and your screen display choices. Login cookies last for two days, and screen options cookies last for a year. If you select “Remember Me”, your login will persist for two weeks. If you log out of your account, the login cookies will be removed.

If you edit or publish an article, an additional cookie will be saved in your browser. This cookie includes no personal data and simply indicates the post ID of the article you just edited. It expires after 1 day.

### Embedded content from other websites

Articles on this site may include embedded content (e.g. videos, images, articles, etc.). Embedded content from other websites behaves in the exact same way as if the visitor has visited the other website.

These websites may collect data about you, use cookies, embed additional third-party tracking, and monitor your interaction with that embedded content, including tracing your interaction with the embedded content if you have an account and are logged in to that website.

### Analytics

## Who we share your data with

## How long we retain your data

If you leave a comment, the comment and its metadata are retained indefinitely. This is so we can recognize and approve any follow-up comments automatically instead of holding them in a moderation queue.

For users that register on our website (if any), we also store the personal information they provide in their user profile. All users can see, edit, or delete their personal information at any time (except they cannot change their username). Website administrators can also see and edit that information.

## What rights you have over your data

If you have an account on this site, or have left comments, you can request to receive an exported file of the personal data we hold about you, including any data you have provided to us. You can also request that we erase any personal data we hold about you. This does not include any data we are obliged to keep for administrative, legal, or security purposes.

## Where we send your data

Visitor comments may be checked through an automated spam detection service.

## Your contact information

## Additional information

### How we protect your data

### What data breach procedures we have in place

### What third parties we receive data from

### What automated decision making and/or profiling we do with user data

### Industry regulatory disclosure requirements

* * *

Really Simple SSL and Really Simple SSL add-ons do not process any personal identifiable information, so the GDPR does not apply to these plugins or usage of these plugins on your website. You can find our privacy policy [here](https://really-simple-ssl.com/privacy-statement/).
